Preliminary Guide to the AIDS Action Foundation records, 1984-2006 MS2212
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1987-1999; Series 7; 3 Linear Feet
  - Photographs Houston Event, 1999 September 23; Series 7 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Photographs Ron Dellums, undated; Series 7 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Photographs AIDS Walk Conference, undated; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 7 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Photographs various events, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Photographs unidentified, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Images: Premotion, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Photographs staff, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Photographs AIDS Action Council Board, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 7 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, undated; Series 7 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Audio and visual materials, 1988-2001; Series 8; 7.5 Linear Feet
  This series contains primarily video cassettes along with a few CDs and audio cassettes. The videos are comprised of news footage, documentaries, and awards ceremonies. These items are dated from 1988-2001.
  - The Ryan White Story, 1988; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 17)
  - The Indiana Kid profile in courage CBS News, 1989 January 7; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 16)
  - AIDS Program American Medical Television Washington Medical Rounds, 1990 August 26; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 25)
  - Ryan White Music Video "Colors", 1990 December 17; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 41)
  - Donahue Show Ryan White in memorium, 1990 September; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 17)
  - Project Face to Face Smithsonian Institution Experimental Gallery Exhibition: We invite you to see the faces and hear the voices of people living with AIDS, 1991; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 15)
  - AIDS Action News Spots Sonja Live with Dan Bross "HIV and Immigration", 1991 June 24; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 30)
  - AIDS Action News Spots AAC 2 and 3 Wash. Hilton Mtg. Part 2, 1993 December 10; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 27)
  - AIDS Action News Spots AAC 2 and 3 Wash. Hilton Mtg. Part I, 1993 December 10; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 6)
  - AIDs Action promotion AAF #7, 1994 May 10; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 11)
  - AIDs Action promotion AAF #6, 1994 May 10; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 12)
  - WTHR Channel 13 Ryan White Foundation, 1994 September 26; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 20)
  - AIDS Action News Spots CBS Evening News, 1994 June 17-18; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 29)
  - AIDS Action News Spots ABC News W/ Christine Lubinski "AIDS", 1994 February 16; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 7)
  - Ryan White Foundation Polo Match, 1994 August 27; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 8)
  - Interview with Cathy Harrison WTHR TV 27 11AM Kristianna, 1995 November 1; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 34)
  - "Jeannie White reacts to jesse Helms comments on AIDS Funding", 1995 July 5; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 21)
  - AIDS Action News Spots MacNeil/Lehrer Report Re: Murray, 1995 April 13; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 31)
  - AIDS Action News Spots News Channel 8, Live "Daytalk" Re: Medicaid with Christine Lubinski, 1995 October 20; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 32)
  - AIDS Programs Northwest AIDS Foundation Mens Campaign, 1995 March; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 2)
  - AIDS Action News Spots CNN Ryan White Care Act, 1995 July 5; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 28)
  - Senate floor C-Span Ryan White Care Act Debate, 1995 July; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 1)
  - AIDS: In a New Light, 1995 May 18; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 32)
  - First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton remarks to the Ryan White Foundation, 1995 March 13; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 38)
  - AIDS Program President's Clintons's Message World AIDS Day, 1995; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 37)
  - WRTV-6 "This Week in Indiana" (AIDS) (full show), 1995 July 9; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 8)
  - First Lady Hillary Rodham Clinton remarks to Ryan White Foundation, 1995 March 13; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 15)
  - Jeanne White Ryan White Foundation "Star Fleet Challenge of the Heart", 1995 September 18; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 22)
  - AIDS in Rural Communities education for prevention, 1995 September 19; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 36)
  - Demonstration video, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 13)
  - Edy's Story: AIDS Changes Everything Linda's Story: HIV has the power, 1996; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 14)
  - AIDS Programs Democratic National Committee Gala Democractic National Committee, 1996 May 8; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 10)
  - Jeanne White Ryan Whites' Legacy part of the Victories Series, 1996; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 18)
  - Spearhead "Positive", 1996 September 25; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 1)
  - Spearhead "Positive", 1996 October 21; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 2)
  - Leadership Awards NEWs Channel 8 TV AA National Leadership Awards, 1996 May 13; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 12)
  - WRTV Channel 6, 1996 July 23; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 23)
  - Ryan White Care Act, 1996 May 20-21; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 26)
  - The Dream Team Quilt in the Capital Celebration of Sharing, 1996 November 26; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 28)
  - Excellence in Indiana Ryan White, 1996 February 2; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 7)
  - City of Jacksonville "Ryan White Care Act" Title I, 1996 June 6; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 24)
  - Victories: Jeanne White Ryan White's Legacy part of the victories series, 1996; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 11)
  - CNN Early Prime CDC #'s (released at State of AIDS Forum), 1997 July 14; Series 8 (Box 82, Videocassette 1)
  - CNN Today (Zingale) Needle Exchange, 1997 February 19; Series 8 (Box 82, Videocassette 2)
  - Statement of AAC Board Member Jimmy Loyce of APLA, 1997; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 30)
  - AIDS Action dinner video project Jimmy Loyce segemet AIDS Project L.A., 1997; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 31)
  - Statement of AAC Board Member Larry Kessler, AAC Boston, MA, 1997; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 32)
  - Statement of AAC Board member Dr. Victoria Sharp of HIVCCC, Beth Israel Med Ctr. NY, 1997; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 33)
  - Washington Journal - Christine Lubinski vs. Christine O'Donnell Savior's Alliance for Lifting the Truth Re: AIDS Funding in Clinton FY 98 Budget, 1997 February 11; Series 8 (Box 82, Videocassette 5)
  - AIDS Action cds, discs, audio cassettes, 1997, undated; Series 8 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - AIDS and the Issues, 1997 December 1; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 18)
  - Ryan's Angel Awards, 1997 December 5; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 29)
  - Dream Team Overview, 1997 November 15; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 27)
  - WRTV Channel 6, 1997 February 25; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 24)
  - AIDS Action Video clips, 1997; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 39)
  - Statement of AAC Board member Gloria Smith - Columbus AIDS Task Force, used for production of AA Video, 1997; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 40)
  - CBS Evening News, 1997 April 06; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 16)
  - AIDS Action Video clips, 1997; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 35)
  - Jeanne White Youth in Action New Paltz NY, 1997 May; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 14)
  - AIDS Action Awards acceptance speech by Vice President Al Gore, 1997; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 22)
  - News interview Christine Lubinski of AAC, on CDC AIDS Mortality statistics WJLA TV Channel 7, 1997 February 28; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 20)
  - Jerry Levin comments about Tim Boggs for AIDS Action Awards, 1997; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 33)
  - USA Live Entertainment (non-sports) 1 of 2, 1997 March 18; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 6)
  - AIDS Action News Spots BET Zingale, Loyce, Hall, 1997 April 18; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 36)
  - Leadership Awards CNN News -AA Leadership Awards Re: Medicaid expansion. Al Gore., 1997 July 10; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 5)
  - AIDS Action News Spots Channel 9, DC News John O'Connor on Living with HIV: "Effect of Diagnosis", 1997 July 22; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 8)
  - AIDS Action News Spots NBC Channel 4 News CDC Report, 1997 July 14; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 9)
  - Youth Panel, 1997; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 20)
  - Leadership Awards CNN News National Leadership Awards, 1997 April 10; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 11)
  - Ali Gertz in her own words, 1997 August 11; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 1)
  - Jeanne White 's book signing, 1997 April 15; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 22)
  - Jeanne White AIDS Action Awards Ceremony, 1999 April 5; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 29)
  - AIDS Action Awards, 1998 April 6; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 30)
  - AIDS Action Awards, 1998 April 6; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 31)
  - AIDS Action Awards, 1998 April 6; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 32)
  - Victories: Jeanne White, 1998 January; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 10)
  - Love Heals Ali Gertz "In Her Own Words", 1998 May 19; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 29)
  - HIV/AIDS and Latinos, 1999 September; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 34)
  - CNN Persp "Russian Factor", 1999 August 22; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 8)
  - AIDS Action awards recipients, 1999 April 5; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 38)
  - Starbucks AIDS Action Award Ceremony, 1999 March 9; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 17)
  - Ryan White Foundation, Rae's Story, It's Real, Moldy Bread, Got it, Going' On, and One Night Stand, 1999 November 29; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 34)
  - Ryan White Foundation, Rae's Story, It's Real, Moldy Bread, Got it, Going' On, and One Night Stand, 1999 November 29; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 35)
  - AIDS Action Awards acceptance speech by Vice President Al Gore, 1999 April 5; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 28)
  - Ryan White: Rae's Story, It's Real, Moldy Bread, Got it Goin' On, One Night Stand, 2000 June 13; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 5)
  - Ryan White: Rae's Story, It's Real, Moldy Bread, Got it Goin' On, One Night Stand, 2000 June 13; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 6)
  - AIDS Action National Leadership Awards, 2000 April 10; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 25)
  - AIDS Action National Leadership Awards, 2000 April 10; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 26)
  - AIDS Action National Leadership Awards, 2000 April 10; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 27)
  - AIDS Action awards recipients, 2000 April 6; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 23)
  - AIDS Action caucasions mixed gender Things people in our country are concerned about, 2000 June 8; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 36)
  - AIDS Action African American men Things people in our country are concerned about, 2000 June 8; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 37)
  - AIDS Action Hispanic Women, 2000 June 15; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 40)
  - AIDS Action Caucasion Men, 2000 June 15; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 41)
  - AIDS Action 2001, Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 33)
  - AIDS Action 2001, 2001 April 23; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 39)
  - AIDS Action awards recipients, 2001 April 19; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 42)
  - Craig Miller Awards: AIDS Action, 2001 April; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 43)
  - Non AAC 100 MTV Tribute to Pedro Z, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 2)
  - Non AAC 100 MTV Tribute to Pedro Z, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 3)
  - Non AAC 100 MTV Tribute to Pedro Z, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 4)
  - Edu. Of Children and Young People on HIV/AIDs, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 7)
  - AAC 7 World AIDS Day Dan Bross and Chris Lubinski, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 9)
  - HIV/AIDS and African Americans, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 13)
  - Ryan White Foundation RSA AIDS Awareness Days, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 15)
  - AAC 7 World AIDS Day Dan Bross and Chris Lubinski, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 19)
  - AIDS Action Video, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 21)
  - AIDS Action Satellite session "U.S. Domestic HIV/AIDS Agenda", undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 23)
  - AIDS Action, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 24)
  - Pedro Non AAC 15 "Real World" last episode with Pedro, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 35)
  - Beckholds AIDS Awareness Boeing - L. Schwitters, undated; Series 8 (Box 84, Videocassette 38)
  - Noble County AIDS Task Force, Inc. AIDS Teen Drama group Straightway, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 3)
  - Terre Haute North Winterguard, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 4)
  - What Begins with [image of ribbon], undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 5)
  - Richardson Carroll Productions Unsung Heroes show 10, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 7)
  - Terre Haute North Winterguard, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 9)
  - Turning Point with Barbara Walters, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 10)
  - Jeanne White on Rolonda Show, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 11)
  - Rolonda "Flashback 1986" Jeanne White/Ryan White Foundation show #4017, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 12)
  - Get Real Alcohol /AIDS Peer Education Grape!, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 16)
  - Sex Education in America AIDS and Adolescence, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 17)
  - The Southwest Virginia Theater for Youth "The Man in the mirror", undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 18)
  - Sroka Disney Oprah, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 19)
  - AIDS Programs "AIDS Changing the Rules" hosted by Ron Reagan, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 24)
  - AIDS Action News Spots AAC 1 from the Hill Fed. Aids Pol. Incl. Chris Lubinski, undated; Series 8 (Box 85, Videocassette 26)
  - AIDS Programs Non AAC 65 "In Our Own Words" Teens and AIDS copy 1 of 2, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 3)
  - Pedro Non AAC 100 MTV, Tribute to Pedro Z. Copy 2 of 3, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 4)
  - AIDS Progras Executive Video Memo Re: AIDS In The Workplace seminar, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 10)
  - Song of Superman, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 13)
  - AIDS Action Promotion AIDS Action in Action, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 14)
  - AIDS Awarenewss Day with Dan Bross McNeil Lerher, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 15)
  - Working with Communities to make safe sex and abstinence cool to teens CDC, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 16)
  - Ryan White Foundation RSA AIDS Awareness Days, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 18)
  - Journey Toward Compassion: AIDS and the Church, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 19)
  - Newsclips RE: world AIDS day and Angel Awards presentation, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 21)
  - Time Out Arsenio Hall and Magic Johnson, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 22)
  - Victories: Jeanne White, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 25)
  - AIDS Action update, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 30)
  - Camp Heartland, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 31)
  - Camp Heartland Summer Camping for kids affected by HIV/AIDS AIDS Awareness Education, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 33)
  - AIDS save our future protect our children, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 34)
  - Hillary Clinton remarks to Ryan White Foundation, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 35)
  - Hillary Clinton remarks to Ryan White Foundation, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 36)
  - KTOO Healthy Students Bill DeSouza/Cuvy, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 37)
  - The AIDS Memorial Grove Today Show, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 39)
  - Cristiani show, undated; Series 8 (Box 83, Videocassette 40)
  - American Red Cross Knox County Chapter Camp Itsamongus, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 1)
  - Aids and Substance Abuse Speakers Network Media Video, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 3)
  - Carrie the Message, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 4)
  - Carrie the Message, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 5)
  - Respect Yourself Protect Yourself, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 6)
  - Homes Ryan White Conference D.C., undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 9)
  - Ryan White Foundation RSA AIDS Awareness Day raw footage, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 12)
  - In Our Own Words, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 13)
  - Hillary Clinton's Remarks For Ryan White Foundation, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 14)
  - Community update from the 12th World AIDS conference, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 19)
  - It couldn't happen to me.. But it did, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 20)
  - It couldn't happen to me.. But it did, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 21)
  - "A Day of Compassion" show #4187, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 23)
  - Camp Itsamongus, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 25)
  - Saving A Generation A video series for HIV and AIDS Education, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 26)
  - Unreasoning Fear The Ryan White Story, undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 27)
  - "Considering Condoms", undated; Series 8 (Box 86, Videocassette 28)
    An Educational video developed by the National Education Assocation Health Information Network.
  - CNBC Financial News, undated; Series 8 (Box 82, Videocassette 3)
  - Graham/Kessler sound bites, undated; Series 8 (Box 82, Videocassette 4)
- Other AIDS organizations, 1998-2005, many undated; Series 9; 4.5 Linear Feet
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains correspondence, meeting materials, reports, and publications related to other organizations working to end AIDS in America and throughout the World. These records date from 1998-2005.
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Global AIDS, 1999; Series 9 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - AETC [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - AETC General [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 39)
  - AETC General [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - AETC Great Lakes to Tennesse Valley [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - AETC Lobby days evaluation forms [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - AETC Medical College of PA Hospital [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - AETC Medical College of Virginia [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - AETC Mid-Atlantic [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - AETC Mid-Atlantic - DC [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - AETC Mid-Atlantic - MD [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - AETC Misc. [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - AETC Montefiore Medical Center [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - AETC National Migrant Resources [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - AETC Mountain Plain [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - AETC New Jersey AIDS Ed. and Training [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - AETC New Mexico AIDS Ed. [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - AETC New York and The Virgin Island [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - AETC New York State University [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - AETC Northwest AIDS Ed. [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - AETC Northwest [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - AETC Pacific AIDS [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - AETC Partnership People [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - AETC Philadelphia AIDS Consortium [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - AETC program [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - AETC program [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - AETC Richmond AIDS Ministry [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - AETC San Francisco General Hospital [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - AETC Seattle-King County [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - AETC Southeast [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - AETC State of Montana Health and Human Services [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - AETC Texas/Oklahoma [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - AETC Tennessee AIDS Ed. [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - AETC University of Washington [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - AETC University of Pittsburgh [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - AETC University of VA Health Sciences Center [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - AETC VA Commonwealth [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - AETCs [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], 2005; Series 9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AETC Obtaining consumer input in the AETCs [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], 1995 July 25; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - AETC Pacific [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - AETC Pennsylvania [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - AIDS Policy Center position paper, undated; Series 9 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - AETC Puerto Rico [AIDS Education and Training Centers National Resource Center], undated; Series 9 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - AIDS Watch, undated; Series 9 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Alameda County health care serv., undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Alaskan AIDS assistance, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - AMCHP Statement [Association of Maternal and Child Health Programs], undated; Series 9 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - American Medical Association, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - brainstorming for 2005 ADAP proposal, Series 9 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Brown University, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Bureau of Health Resources Development, undated; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 19)